Finding Aid for Marian Carr papers, 1957-1963
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Marian Carr papers 1957-1963
Carr, Marian
0.3 linear feet
8589 Aa 2
Member of the Ann Arbor Human Relations Commission; minutes and other materials relating to race relations in Ann Arbor, Michigan.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The collection was the gift of Marian Carr (donor no. 6527 ) and came to the library in 1980.
The collection is open to research.
Marian Carr was a member of the Ann Arbor Human Relations Commission, 1957-1960. She was also a member of the Ann Arbor-Washtenaw County American Civil Liberties Union.
The collection contains minutes, correspondence, clippings, and printed material dealing largely with her work with the Ann Arbor Human Relations Commission and the problem of race relations in Ann Arbor, Michigan. The Commission was particularly involved in issues of discrimination in housing and employment.
Subjects:
African Americans--Michigan.; American Civil Liberties Union. Ann Arbor-Washtenaw County Branch.; Ann Arbor (Mich.). Human Relations Commission.; Civil rights--Michigan--Ann Arbor.; Discrimination in employment--Michigan--Ann Arbor.; Discrimination in housing--Michigan--Ann Arbor.
- Ann Arbor Human Relations Commission
  - Minutes and related materials
    - 1957 (Box 1)
    - 1958 (Box 1)
    - 1959 (Box 1)
    - 1960 (Box 1)
    - 1963 (Box 1)
  - Clippings (Box 1)
  - Miscellanea (Box 1)
- Ann Arbor-Washtenaw County American Civil Liberties Union
  - Miscellanea (Box 1)